I said yesterday after body North Pole
there is no because it's a chance of a
lifetime
finish that are for a marathon
to be able to go even though I've always
wanted to go to the North Pole and to be
able to go because of running something
I really love to do it's it's just
amazing
so it's sort of my ticket so it's I feel
so blessed also you know it's a race for
a lifetime
a lot of destination areas such as let's
say Kona Boston and all these others
even wrong but to be able to go to the
North Pole and actually your race there
how many people do you know have done it
so to be able to do it you'll be able to
have this opportunity you know you just
don't say no this new challenge means
the world to me
you know of a year ago I find but I
found myself at a crossroads
jump into an entire year and little did
I know that it'll also open up an
opportunity like this being able to go
to the North Pole be able to race and
make history for my country I've had so
many medals I've been to a lot of play
mystery but this one is super excited
I've never done it I've never even run
in snow before so it's definitely a new
challenge something I've not used to but
definitely up to it
[Music]
you